newshub.com.ng 2016-06-22

# Privacy Policy - News Hub

**As of September 1st, 2014**

**Newshub.com.ng** Â  has prepared this Privacy Policy to help you understand more about how we collect, use, and disclose information that we collect about consumers through our web and mobile services, which we refer to in this Privacy Policy collectively as the â€œServices.â€

This Privacy Policy does not cover information that we collect about you outside of our normal consumer services. For example, it does not cover information that we collect in news reporting or as a part of our business arrangements. Also, this Privacy Policy does not cover information that you voluntarily make public, such as by posting it in a publicly accessible place on the Internet **.**

**What information do you collect about me?**

The information that we collect about you falls into these general categories:

â€¢ Information that you provide. We may collect information that you choose to provide to us (including in comments or other user content that you submit to us or when you subscribe to our newsletter(s)). This may include information such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, year of birth, gender, zip code, country, postal address, , user name, password, and password reminder questions and answers. We may ask you for information when you register or subscribe, or at other timesâ€”such as when you enter a contest or participate in a promotion, when you provide content, or when you order products from us.

â€¢ Automated information. Using technologies that are widely used on the Internet, such as cookies, web beacons, and other technologies, we also may automatically collect information about your computer or mobile device and online activity when you access the Services. For example, when you visit thedailybeast.com, we may collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and operating system, as well as information about which pages you visit and the page, if any, that referred you to our sites or that you visit after our sites. Similarly, when you use our mobile applications, we may collect information about your mobile device, such as the type of mobile device you use or your device identifier.

â€¢ Location information. When you use the Services, we may collect information about your location separately from your address or other information that you provide to us explicitly. For instance, we may use the GPS feature of your mobile device or your IP address to help determine your geographic location. If you prefer that we not know your geographic location, you will have the option to disable the function when you first use the service in which we collect information about your location (or later, if your mobile device allows you to change the settings after initial download). Disabling the geo location function may prevent you from using certain features of our Services that require location information.

â€¢ Social networking information. If you log-in to Newshub.com.ng through a social networking account (e.g., Facebook or Twitter), we may collect information about you from that social networking account, including your name, email address, birthday, profile photograph, and other information associated with your social networking account.

How do you use this information?

We use the information that we collect about you for these purposes

â€¢ For editorial purposes, such as in connection with our news reporting;

â€¢ to contact you to provide information about **Newshub.com.ng** or other products or services in which we believe you may be interested, including legal notices or information about changes to this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use;

â€¢ To manage your account;

â€¢ To provide you with the products and services you request;

â€¢ To respond to your requests, questions, and comments;

â€¢ To perform business analyses or for other purposes to improve the quality of our business, the products and services we offer, including through surveys and questionnaires;

â€¢ To deliver targeted advertising, as described below;

â€¢ As we believe is necessary to protect our rights and the rights of others, including by enforcing our Terms of Use;

â€¢ And as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.

We also do research on our usersâ€™ demographics, interests, and behaviour to help us operate our services, for other business purposes, and in connection with our display of advertising (which we describe below). This research is based on the information you provide to us including upon registration during a promotion, in surveys, and on your use of our services.

**With whom do you share this information?**

We may share the information that we collect about you through the Services in these ways

â€¢ with authorized service providers that help us provide the Services or perform other business functions for us, such as sending emails or hosting web services (but these service providers are not permitted to use personally identifiable information that we provide for any purpose other than to provide service to us);

â€¢ in the context of contests or other promotions in which we identify an outside entity, with the identified entity;

â€¢ with select third parties for the third partiesâ€™ direct marketing purposes, although you may choose up front and at no cost that we not share personally identifiable information that we have collected about you for these purposes by emailing us at help [at] newshub.com.ng;

â€¢ to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, in response to a request for cooperation from law enforcement or another government agency, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

â€¢ when we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or as otherwise required by law;

â€¢ to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements, or otherwise protect or defend our rights or property or the rights or property of others, or the safety of the public;

â€¢ in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale;

â€¢ in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable form;

â€¢ and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.

In addition, if you choose to participate in social features on the Services, such as commenting on a story or chatting with other users, any information that you submit will become public. It may become accessible through search engines or, if you sign in using credentials from a third-party social networking service, to users on that service. Unless otherwise noted, we do not limit the distribution of information that you share using these features.

**How do you decide which advertisements to show me on the Services?**

The Services are offered to you free of charge because we cover the cost of providing our Services by displaying advertisements. Many of these advertisements are targeted, which means that advertisers tell us the type of audience they want to reach (for example, men over 25 years old). We will display the advertisement to users meeting those criteria, but we never provide the advertiser with information about the specific individuals who receive the ads. The targeted ads on the Services may be provided by us, or they may be provided by a third-party vendor. You can learn more about targeted ads, including how to opt out of receiving them, below.

Does this Privacy Policy apply to information collected through third-party offerings?

We sometimes partner with third parties that operate platforms or offer services that you can use to access or otherwise interact with our content and offerings. For example, you can access newshub.com.ng on your Apple iPad or iPhone and mobile phones. Similarly, we may include in some of our Services features that integrate with third-party social networking services or other third-party services. To do this, we may include in our web pages and apps code from the social networking service provider or other third party. This code may allow the service provider to collect information about your activities. If you are logged into social networking or other third-party services at the time, the service providers may also be able to identify you in connection with that information.

Although this Privacy Policy will apply to our use of information collected about you through these co-branded offerings, we do not control the privacy practices of our third-party partners. As a result, we want you to be aware that when you use these offerings you may be providing information to both us and our partner, and you should review the partnerâ€™s privacy policy to be sure that you know how it will use any data that it collects.

**Do you collect information from children?**

We would not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected any personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information from our database promptly.

**What choices do I have regarding your use of information about me?**

Email messages. If you do not wish to receive emailed promotional material from us, you can email us at help [at] thedailybeast.com. Please note that, even if you opt out of receiving promotional emails from us, we may still contact you to provide you with non-commercial messages, such as legal notices. Also, if you opt out, we may not provide to you non-promotional material, such as our emailed newsletters and other content.

Sharing of information collected online. If you would like to opt out of our sharing of personal information that we collect about you through the Services, you can make a request to cancel your registration by emailing us at **help@newshub.com.ng** , explaining your request, and providing your name and email address. Please understand that it may take us a reasonable amount of time to cancel your registration after we receive your request and that your cancellation will not apply to our uses of information about you prior to our receipt of the request. If you make a cancellation request, you should not access the Services again, because we may not be able to preserve your opt-out preferences if you continue to access the Services after we cancel your registration

**What happens when this Privacy Policy changes?**

We may update this Privacy Policy in the future. We will notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by sending a notice to the e-mail address you provided to us or by placing a notice on Newshub website.

**Who should I contact if I have questions about this Privacy Policy?**

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, you may contact us at: [**help@newshub.com.ng**](mailto:help@newshub.com.ng)
